-[Caine]: On the next episode
of "The Amazing Digital Circus,"
everyone gets guns!
That's really all there is to it!
[laughing raucously]
It's the showdown
of the century!
Century! CENTURY!
Three teams face off in a non-stop,
action-filled hootenanny
that you won't want to miss!
-[Jax]: I've been waiting for this
my whole life!
-[Gangle]: Caine, I don't think
this is a good idea.
-[Ragatha]: Yeah, I'm not sure this is
really what we need right now.
[blam!]
[air whistling]
-[Caine]: Only one team
will come out victorious
in our longest episode yet!
Over 33 minutes?
Holy moly!
You couldn't cut that
down at all?!
-[Gooseworx]:
Making shows is really hard
when you have a cast this big.
-[Kinger]: Wait, who was that?
-[Mr. Gun]: Who am I?
I'm Mr. Gun!
-[Kinger]: Not you, Mr. Gun.
The other voice.
-[Zooble]: Uh, mister who?
-[Mr. Gun]: I was supposed
to be in this episode,
but Caine removed me
for being too gun!
-[Zooble]:
Yeah, okay, whatever.
-[Pomni]: Are we just all
in this trailer?
-[Ep. 3 Trailer Narrator]:
And I'm still here, too --
the Episode 3 trailer narrator.
-[Ragatha]: Why do these trailers
have their own continuity?
-[Caine]:
So, what are you waiting for?
Buy your tickets today
and come down to the biggest event
in Digital Circus history!
-[Info Narrator]:
Tickets not really for sale.
You can watch the latest episode
and all previous episodes
of "The Amazing Digital Circus"
anytime at home or on the go
on your computer book or device.
If you have any
further questions or concerns,
dial 8888888888888888888888881.
Ask your parent's permission
before going to hell.
-[Caine]: Be there or be rere!
[sighs]
I wish guns were real.